I don't want nobody to get killed
I come and get you, I'm always ready to fight
So don't take all of the blame, we're always wet
Oh, I don't take all of the blame, you always do
There will always be something you cannot control
We will overcome, your salvation has begun
Those suns, those lights, such a mess, so lovely
Don't kill your walls, you make me realize who I need
I'll be there, hold on, the changes in power
So where are you now?
I'll reach you, my top, the shadows of the earth
Illusions are born
The golden end is still wrong, but I know it's a pain
I'll admit, I'm still human after all
Don't want to save you for the control
About your precious worth
This scar may respond to your call
What are you waiting for?
Activate the curse and kill him
Hurry!
That's an order
I can't
You damn rookie!
The hell!
What was that?
You had him
Why didn't you make the kill?
I think he...
Gorin, are you alright?
Worry about yourself, you idiot
Did you forget this is a war zone?
Keep your eyes on the enemy
Hey moron, what's the deal?
You had that bloodsucker right where you wanted him
Did you forget how to use your gear?
What's wrong?
You don't look so good
Well, you...
I'm sorry
But if that's who I think it is
My family's with the vampires
Tell me!
Is it really you, Mikaela?
It is you
Mika
I'm so sorry
I abandoned you
No, that's not true
Oh, this might be the sweetest thing I've ever seen
And just look at how much dear Yuichiro has sprouted
What a fateful and unexpected reunion for the three of us
Brings back so many memories
It's almost enough to bring tears to my eyes
So, what's the plan?
Your friend is most likely being manipulated by these humans
I'm going to save him
From the hands of these traitorous dogs?
Yes
But he's one of them
Do you really think a human could befriend us?
I'm sure he'd rather die
Ah, I know
I can do for him what Cruel did for you, Mika
One drop of my blood and Yuichiro will be reborn
If you so much as try to lay a finger on him
I'll kill you
Oh, come now
I was only kidding
You really need to learn to take a joke with your boy
Now, why don't I help you rescue your princess?
I'll deal with the other livestock while you rescue Yuichiro
Just leave it to me
All you need to worry about is getting him out of harm's way
I'm not surprised you've made new friends
You've always been such a kind soul
But sometimes you can be too nice
So much so that people take advantage of you
The truth is
These friends you've made are faking it
They're greedy and deceitful
All of them
Very well
It's been decided
All of the humans will die except for the long-lost lamb Yuichiro
Looks like I got here just in time
Sorry I'm running late, third progenitor
Ah, Crowley, so glad you could make it to the party
Him again
I took a little detour on the way over here
Of course
Was anything interesting going on?
Well, now that you're here
The game I had planned won't be quite as much fun
But
We could play a new one
It's called Take Them Alive
We'll capture the Moon Demon Company
And make them our livestock
I could get behind that
Damn
We were in trouble before this guy showed up
I've got no choice
Everyone!
Prepare to retreat!
No, we can't just run away, damn it
Mika's my family
I won't leave them with these monsters
Shut up
You're willing to let your comrades die for a vampire?
You
Let's go
Please, you
Fall back
Keep your formation and retreat to the second defense line
Come on, don't you want to play?
Break formation!
Damn you!
What the hell's gotten into you?
Die!
You bastard!
Stop you!
What is that idiot thinking?
No, wait!
You are fast, but you've still got a lot to learn
And you should know by now that the injured lion's strike is never quite as sharp
Lieutenant Colonel!
Move!
Try the hurry!
Oh wow!
Still standing?
Looks like we've got ourselves a hero
Are you okay?
Don't worry
I'll be fine
These bastards don't have any intention of letting us get to Gurren
In that case, we'll just have to kill all of them
Easier said than done, I'm afraid
That's why we're having all this trouble in the first place
The only way out of here is as livestock or corpses
So what's it going to be?
Well, we're waiting
Focus!
What are you doing?
Get on your feet!
Yeah, sorry
Well, hello
So we meet again
This time I'm not letting you get away from me
Goran!
Watch out!
I've waited so long to get a taste of your-
You see?
This is what I meant about taking a chute
Be sure to call me if you need a hand
Mika
Let's go
Leave everything behind and escape with me
Huh?
What do you mean escape?
Answer me
Why are you with the vampire who killed our family?
Never mind that
You!
Don't take your eyes off the enemy
Hey!
Let go of me!
Stop playing, Mika!
Tell me what's going on
You at least owe me that much!
The short version is that you shouldn't be here
Not with the humans
They're just using me
What?
That's the dumbest thing I've ever heard
Shut up and put me down!
The humans are using me?
What are you saying?
Aren't you still alive?
Wait, you are human, right?
Don't tell me that they changed you
Is this because of me?
Is this because I abandoned you?
No!
You didn't do anything wrong
Then why, Mika?
Let's just go
It isn't safe here
Please, you
Come with me
No, I'm staying until it's over
It's just
They're friends
I can't leave
You're wrong!
They only see you as a tool
Please, you
Trust me
I'm trying to save you
Before it's too late
Shinua!
Please, don't look back
There's nothing behind you
Nothing important
Just come with me
Let go of her!
Come on!
They're in trouble!
There's nothing you can do to help them!
Get off me!
You can't!
Just forget about them!
In the end, they'll betray you and toss you aside!
Mitsuva!
Let's get out of here before they capture you!
I won't run away again!
Goju! Run!
Hush, livestock don't speak. Please call them off.
Hurry, Mika!
You should be worried about yourself. It's too late for them now.
You? What's the matter?
Murder, judge!
Hush!
Talk to me, Ashura Maru.
About what?
What's happening to me?
You're not trying to possess me, are you?
No, this has nothing to do with me.
It seems we've got a big problem on our hands.
I've been around for a while, but I never thought I'd be terrified of a monster inside the human I was possessing.
There, you see how the clouds are parting?
It's as if the heavens have opened to shine judgment on this cursed world.
You know, I think your friend is right.
Listen to him and escape while you can.
This might be your one and only chance.
If you stay here, you won't be human for long.
Wait, what?
I'm afraid it's too late.
The non-human part of you is about to lose all control.
And so it begins.
It's true.
The humans have been using him all along.
Snap out of it!
Please, you!
Leave this place with me!
You!
Get your foot!
Oh, my God!
Iramos!
prendo!
Let's just stand last chance.
Thank you, Angel!
I don't know what that is, but it doesn't look good.
That's a lot of damage. Very impressive.
No, Yu, stop!
You went and got my clothes all dirty.
Oh.
That's one creepy monster.
Seriously, it's so revolting, I've completely lost my appetite.
What is that thing, Farid?
I don't know. Do you?
Nah, we'll just have to wait and see.
Let me guess.
This is the result of human experimentation, isn't it?
Tell me, where does that infinite greed of yours come from?
Honestly, it scares me.
Besides, you always seem to be losing control of it.
See?
Sinners. Sinners must die. Sinners must all be annihilated.
No.
Shinoa!
You're the only one who can help him. There's still a chance that he can come back.
No, you don't do it!
You'd never be able to forgive yourself!
Why? Why did you... save me?
Shut up, human. This is happening because you used him!
Damn it. My injury won't heal.
Annihilate.
Every sinner.
Shinilla!
What are you waiting for?
Our lives depend on you!
Go!
Yuu, stop it!
Please, you have to!
For all of us are going to die!
Don't you dare touch him!
Get your filthy hands off my family!
Stop it!
Please, you!
Don't do it!
Come back to us!
You!
I'm right here!
You're okay.
Damn you humans and your treachery.
You'll pay for this.
So how do you like my trump card?
For a rookie, he puts on one hell of a show.
Sadly for you, he didn't really achieve anything.
I wouldn't be so sure.
He's managed to distract you.
And that was our main objective all along.
Uh-oh, they've seen us.
But not soon enough to make a difference.
Destroy our enemies, the Akomaru.
Oh, and try not to hit Gurren, okay?
Boom.
That was too close for comfort.
If it hadn't been for his big mouth,
that'd be a smoking pile of ash right now.
It appears we're surrounded.
Not bad, Lieutenant Colonel.
I suppose Junior Branch garbage has its use.
You're done here.
The Hiragi family will be taking over.
All right, men.
I want those nobles taken alive.
We need to show them once and for all
what happens to anyone
or anything that opposes humanity.
The Japanese Imperial Demon Army
or the might of the Hiragi family.
Here we go.
Let's do it!
Oh my goodness.
Thank you.
Next time on Seraph of the End, everyone's a sinner.